Tổng hợp danh sách các thứ

Thiết kế đồ họa

Typography and Image Creation

Design History and Critical Thinking

Design and Layout

Illustration and Animation

Design Vocabulary

Digital and Analogue Moving Image

Studio Practice I

Studio Practice II

Reading Images I

Reading Images II

Self-Promotion and Packaging I

Visualising Concepts

Self-Promotion and Packaging II

Industry Competition Briefs

Dissertation

Major Project



Check this out: https://youtu.be/yRzfNvdgjhA

Here's a summary of topics that they mention

Design Principles

Colour Theory

Grid

Drawing

Visual Communication

Perspective

Figure

Lettering 1,2

Typography 1,2,3

Sequential

Storyboarding

Identity Design

Branding

Web/ App Design

UX

UI

Landing pages

3D Visualization

Model

Render

Packaging Design

Editorial Design

Exhibit Design

Environmental/ wayfinding

Studio Projects 1,2,3 (Portfolio)

Design History


https://github.com/benedictusdps/MOOC-MBA
https://www.reddit.com/r/graphic_design/comments/153s3e9/self_taught_graphic_design_where_to_start/
https://www.reddit.com/r/graphic_design/comments/iruqu3/discussion_on_a_selftaught_graphic_design_syllabus/


https://ocw.mit.edu/search/?d=Architecture&s=department_course_numbers.sort_coursenum


https://euangoddard.github.io/clipboard2markdown/

I really suggest you to listen to Vincent Scully class on Youtube. He was a great architecture historian and his class are fascinating. Youtube have some very great video about architecture theory and style that are accessible to a large public too. Im doing a master in architecture history and this is a great discipline !



Advice for somebody who wants to start learning.
Information Requested
Hi guys, I've been reading the sub for a while, but this is my first time posting, so if I do something wrong, tell me. I've been meaning to try to learn the basics and get an understanding of Architecture modeling and such for a while so I know if I want to pursue it in college and beyond.

So what I'm asking is, for a beginner, what is the best software to teach myself with, the best book to learn with, the best videos to watch, etc. I want to learn what I can now to see if it fascinates me beyond just looking and admiring.

Also, I've heard good things about Archicad 17 from a classmate I believe (Long time ago, don't remember now), but I don't know if this is a good one for beginners or whatnot. Also, as you might have guessed, I'm a high schooler, so stuff on the cheaper side would be much appreciated. I don't have $1,000, let alone $5,000.

TL;DR: I'm a beginner, could you share some advice and suggestions?

EDIT 1: Thanks for all the tips guys. I'll be checking everything out when I get the chance. I need to work on getting my license and I also have build season for my FRC Team, so I'll be insanely busy, but I hope to have time after spring break, so I'll probably try everything then. I just wanted to know what I should try in advance. Thanks again for all your helps guys!

For anybody wanting the same advice, but not wanting to read all the comments, the basic ideas given off were as follows:
SketchUp is a great free tool and AutoCAD and Revit are obtainable for free as well if you need something more powerful

There were a few books on theory suggested in the top comment, but reading about an everchanging profession is pointless. They suggested instead asking for a tour of a local firm and talking with them about it.

Just drawing and sketching is a great way to practice without 3D modeling or anything fancy

The Adobe Creative Cloud is full of great tools including Photoshop, Lightroom, etc.


Thêm mục cộng đồng, thực hành và đủ các thứ khác, hình dung đích đến cuối và các thứ?!!